zodee.com.au 2005-10-27

# Zodee - Privacy Policy - Buy Lingerie, Swimwear Sleepwear and Underwear Online

|  |  |   
---  
Help Index  
At Zodee® we value your privacy immensly and it is important what information we collect and use you personal information is understood. This statement is our commitment to the perserving of your privacy and the information we collect and hold.   
Automatic Data Collection  
Due to the nature of the Internet, there is certain information that is transmitted to us automatically, such as you IP address and the browser you are using. This information is collected for purely statistical reasons and part of our ongoing development we track shoppers behaviour on the website but do not attach an personal information to these statistics. Similar information is also transmitted along with any emails sent. This information is not stored.   
Personal Information Submitted  
We do not require shoppers to disclose any information about themselves in order to browse the website, with only minimal information being required in order to make a purchase. Certain information, such as delivery addresses, are stored and redisplayed for your convenience but this information is not accessible to anyone but you.   
Cookies   
In order to shop at Zodee®, we require that cookies be enabled on your browser. However, this is not required in order to simply browse the website. No personal information is stored in that cookie with only a unique identifier that identifies you to us. Due to the nature of cookies, this information is not available to any third party. If you are using a shared computer, such as in an Internet Cafe or Library, then we recommend that you logout from the Zodee® Club and/or remove any cookies from zodee.com.au if you are concerned about your privacy.   
Use of Personal Information   
We will treat the information we collect from you as strictly confidential. Other than as set out below, we will not reveal, disclose, pass on, sell, rent, distribute, share or licence to any third parties any personal information that you may have provided to us unless we have your express consent to do so.   
Exceptions to this are: 

  1. where there are reasonable grounds to believe that disclosure is necessary to prevent a threat to life or health; 
  2. where Zodee® Pty Ltd is required by law to provide your information. 

Mailing List   
When you join the Zodee® club you are automatically added to our mailing list. If you prefer not to receive updates from Zodee®, you can unsubscribe in the members area of the website.   
External Links   
This site contains links to external websites and Zodee® Pty Ltd cannot be held responsible for the Privacy Policies of those sites.   
See also: Security Terms & Conditions  
|  |   
---
